Contact

nachis_103@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nachiketwawoo-2ba7a825 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Embedded Systems Microcontrollers ARM

Certifications

Certified ScrumMaster® (CSM®)

Nachiket Wawoo

Electronics Hardware Designer for Railway Products
Pune

Summary

Employed as a embedded hardware design engineer from 9 years, currently working in railway electronic product design. Experienced in phases of new product development from the conceptual stages to low volume production release. Proficient in simulation using Cadence pSpice, drafting hardware schematics using Mentor Graphics DxDesigner, Cadence OrCAD, directing PCB layout, hardware debugging, design verification & testing, Creative and methodical approach to a problem solving.

Experience

Knorr-Bremse 7 years 1 month

Project Lead April 2017 - Present (3 years 5 months) Pune Area, India

Senior Hardware Design Engineer August 2013 - March 2017 (3 years 8 months) Pune Area, India

Senior Hardware Design Engineer September 2015 - August 2016 (1 year)

Tata Technologies

Embedded Hardware Solutions Developer December 2011 - July 2013 (1 year 8 months)

Being a Embedded Hardware Designer, worked on various products like Automatic Climate Control System, Body Control Modules, Single Cylinder Engine Management System and many more. Can strategically plan, analyze & conceptualize embedded product requirements as per the client's requirement.

MINDA Industries Ltd

Embedded Hardware designer January 2010 - November 2011 (1 year 11 months) pune

Education

Mumbai University

Bachelor of Engineering (BE), Electronics & telecommunication · (2006 - 2009)